xtremeprofits.com 2009-04-08

# Niche Marketing Training & Resources | Niche Marketing Membership

This notice is being provided to you by **_III Websites, LLC_** , Matt Levenhagen and all Partner Sites. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality and security of personal information gathered from potential, current and former customers. The proper handling of personal information continues to be one of our highest priorities. As a valued customer who provides us with nonpublic personal information, we want you to know why we need this information and we want to explain our commitment to protecting the information you provide.

Our postal address is: Upon Request

We can be reached via e-mail at: http://www.jvpal.com/contact.htm

**Customer Information**

We collect and maintain only information necessary for us to be able to provide the services requested by you and to administer your business with us. We may collect nonpublic personal information from the following sources:

  * From you when you complete an application or other form (such as name, address, social security number, or Web Address). 
  * From your transactions with us, our partners, affiliates or others (such as purchasing of e-Books or other material). 
  * From general correspondence that may arise from time to time. 
  * We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations and the e-mail addresses of those who subscribe to our mailing list and newsletter. 

**Sharing Information**

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, it is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

We only share your nonpublic personal information with affiliated or nonaffiliated companies or individuals that perform servicing functions on our behalf or as permitted by law (such as governmental and consumer reporting agencies). In the normal course of our business, we may disclose some or all of the above described information to nonaffiliated companies or individuals that contract with us to perform services or function on our behalf, such as: Record keeping, Distribution of materials, Statement preparation, Computer-related services, Administrative services, or Joint marketing of our products and services.

When we provide nonpublic personal information to a service provider, we require the provider to agree to safeguard your information, to use that information only for the intended purpose and to abide by applicable law.

**Access to Information**

Only employees, management or representatives with a valid business reason have access to your nonpublic personal information. All such persons who work with confidential information are educated on the importance of maintaining the confidentiality and security of the information and are required to abide by our information-handling practices.

With respect to **cookies:**

We do not set any cookies at this time. 

Relating to Use of **Personal Information** :

**If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.**

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by providing us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list we share with other organizations.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.

With respect to **Ad Servers**

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

**Future Changes**

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward.

**Access to the visitors personal information**

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them, financial information (e.g., credit card account information) that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them , a description of information that we maintain about them.

Consumers can access this information by e-mailing us at the above address, or visiting us at <http://www.jvpal.com/contact.htm>.

**Maintenance of Accurate Information**

We strive to maintain accurate, up-to-date customer records in accordance with industry standards. Procedures have been established to keep information current and complete. These procedures include responding to requests to correct information in a timely manner.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information, financial information, unique identifiers, transaction information, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to the site.

Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address, visiting us at <http://www.jvpal.com/contact.htm>. 

**Protection of Information**

We maintain security standards to protect your information, whether written, spoken, or electronic. We update and test our systems to assure protection and integrity of the information. We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site, When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site, We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

**Disclosure of our Privacy Policy**

We recognize and respect the privacy concerns of potential, current and former customers, and are committed to safeguarding nonpublic personal information. As a member of the Online Marketing industry, we are providing you this notice for informational purposes and will update and distribute it as required by law.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number. If it is not resolved with this approach you may contact:

  * The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org 
  * 1State or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau 
  * State or local consumer protection office 
  * The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at <http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm>.
